[
  {
    "question":"1- He fades away and disappears completely as soon as you say his name, who is he?",
  
    "rightAnswer" : "Silence"
  },
  {
    "question":"2- What holds you while you hold it at the same time?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "The shoe"
  },
  {
    "question":"3- Something you give to a million people, and yet it stays with you without losing anything, what is it?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Advice"
  },
  {
    "question":"4- Yellow like gold, its head is used by humans and its leg by animals. What is it?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Wheat ears"
  },
  {
    "question":"5- It has 5 fingers but it is not human, it has skin but it is not an animal, who is it?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "The glove"
  },
  {
    "question":"6- What is the best possible treatment for dandruff?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Baldness"
  },
  {
    "question":"7- Something that does not dissolve in water, and does not live on earth or in the sky, what is it?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Fish"
  },
  {
    "question":"8- If a huge elephant fell into a lake, how would it get out?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Wet"
  },
  {
    "question":"9- Why is the zebra considered an ancient animal?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Because it's black and white"
  },
  {
    "question":"10- What is the function of the ear in the human body?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "To hold the glasses."
  },
  {
    "question":"11- How many letters are there?",
  
    "rightAnswer" : "22"
  },
  {
    "question":"12- What is the color resulting from mixing yellow with blue?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Green"
  },
  {
    "question":"13- How many zeros are there in a trillion?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Twelve"
  },
  {
    "question":"14- How many times has Brazil won the World Cup?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "5 Times"
  },
  {
    "question":"15- What is the disease called the disease of kings?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Gout"
  },
  {
    "question":"16- What is the most dangerous prison in the world, located on an island surrounded by water from all directions?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Alcatraz Prison"
  },
  {
    "question":"17- What is the highest plateau in the world?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Tibet Platosu"
  },
  {
    "question":"18- How many minutes are in 5 hours?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "300 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question":"19- Mention the name of an African country whose name begins with the letter N?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Nigeria"
  },
  {
    "question":"20- Mention the name of an animal that starts with the letter C?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Caterpillar"
  },
  {
    "question":"21- Who is he who remains bound if guarded by one person, but if guarded by many he is freed from his chains?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "Secret"
  },
  {
    "question":"22- What is red and green and looks like half a watermelon?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "The second half of that watermelon"
  },
  {
    "question":"23- What are the three consecutive numbers whose product is 990?",
   
    "rightAnswer" : "9, 10, 11"
  }

]